Marta Bekyarska

Junior Software Engineer

London

mob.: 07596 260 400

martatsoneva@yahoo.com

A well-organised and highly motivated aspiring Software Engineer, currently looking for a challenge in Front End Development. Driven by the passion to solve problems and coding, after 8 years working in hospitality, I took a deeper dive into modern tech. As an intrinsically curious person who likes collaboration, attending meetups and workshops brought me into programming. The in-progress portfolio at https://github.com/MartaBekyarska is the result of several months of self-study. Very excited for an opportunity to develop further and widen my experience in a progressive team.

Skills

ISTQB Certificate Bug reporting and documentation

HTML/CSS/JS/Bootstrap foundation Beginner at Gherkin,

Cucumber Excellent written and verbal

Comfortable with **Git**, **GitHub** communication skills

Understanding of **Agile** Ability to focus on deadlines and methodologies incl. Scrum

Strong attention to **UX** Excellent eye for details

Education

ISTQB Certificate no.: Brightest2018000101

April 2018, London

Testing techniques, Psychology of testing, Test management, Maintenance testing, Black box and White box testing and other testing topics

deliverables

Bachelor Degree in Information Technology, Technical University of Ruse

3 years out of 5 completed. Interrupted due to parental responsibilities. Willing to complete training program similar or equivalent to this.

ICQ Level 3 NVQ Diploma in Hospitality Supervision and Leadership 2014. London

Certificate in English, Westminster Academy

2010 - 2011. London

German Language High School Friedrich Schiller

1997 - 2005, Bulgaria

Experience

Pret A Manger / Team Leader

March 2014 - July 2018, London

Managing a team of 14 members; Preparing audit reports, Banking and Petty Cash Handling; Consistently exceeded personal and store KPIs; Dealt with questions effectively and input data into ICT systems; Conflict resolution and mediation

- Team productivity increased by 15%, saving on labour costs and enhancing store profits.
- Mastered the art of running successful, efficient stores by using past sales data to predict demand and order supplies. This requires a tight balance between ordering enough and reducing waste.
- Improved customer service, leading to more frequent team bonus and higher sales.
- Provided excellent, personal customer service, generating repeat and referral business.

Pret A Manger / Team Member Trainer

September 2010 - March 2014, London

Developed personalised induction schedules for new staff; Participated in hiring decisions and collected hiring feedback from the team; Training new employees on communication and handling customers' complex inquiries; Daily team briefing; Organising staff team awards and events

- Maintained comprehensive, consistently high quality training. Was offered a promotion to a regional trainer manager.
- ❖ Kept all documentation up to date with no exception- led to excellent results on Health and Safety audit checks.

Bulgarian National Police / Call Centre Operator

2006 - 2010, Bulgaria

Responsible for all incoming calls and handling them in a professional and friendly manner; Handling complaints, emergency calls and out-of-hours enquiries; Preparing audit reports on weekly and daily basis; Maintaining the filing system and ensuring all records are kept up to date; Maintained customer database

Hobbies & Interests

I enjoy spending time with my young family, reading, swimming and visiting educational meetups.